

HAMNA IQBAL

FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT



Brooklyn, NY



+1 (347) 265-1549



hamnaikbalkhan@gmail.com

FOLLOW ME



hamnaiqbal



REACTJS

hamnaiqbalkhan

SKILLS

•	
JAVASCRIPT	• • • • •
FIREBASE	• • • • •
WORDPRESS	• • • • •
HTML	• • • • •
CSS	• • • • •
SCSS	• • • • •
SASS	• • • • •
BOOTSTRAP	• • • • •
TAILWIND	• • • • •
BULMA	• • • • •
GIT	• • • • •
SEO	• • • • •
AGILE	• • • • •
SCRUM	
SCROW	• • • • •



ABOUT ME

I am an enthusiastic and passionate web developer from COMSATS University Islamabad. I pursued my BS degree in Computer Science. Although I can code in any field like Desktop Development or even Machine Learning Models, my main specialization is doing Web Development. I pursue perfection in my projects. I put dedication in every project that I do. And I hope my dedication will help me to explore my expertise, and to boost up my career plan.



EDUCATION

> COMSATS UNIVERSITY ISLAMABAD

2018 - 2022

COMSATS University is one of the most prestigious university of Pakistan and the Computer Science is the Specialization of CUI.

> PUNJAB GROUP OF COLLEGES

2016 - 2018

During the two years at this institute, I studied the Faculty of Science in Engineering with a special focus on Mathematics and Physics Subjects.



EXPERIENCE

> STARBUCKS WEBSITE

2021 - 2021

I worked on the Official Starbucks Website for Trinidad and Tobago. The project included complete redesign of their website, and adopting the standard Starbucks style for the country's website.

> NASTECH PROJECT

2020 - 2020

I worked with NASTECH Group of Companies to design and developed their online project management system using WordPress. The system could be used to track the project progress, assign tasks, manage employees, generate reports among other works.

> FREELANCING

2019 - PRESENT

I have done a lot of freelancing Web Projects including WordPress, HTML, CSS, BootStrap, JavaScript etc.



PROJECTS

> STUDENT EDUCATION ASSISTER (FYP) MERN Stack, Flask, Stripe

> DORR - THREAD OF KINDNESS WordPress

> SAFE SPACE HOUSING WordPress

> **FOODIES WEBSITE** ReactJS, Bootstrap

> ADD TO CART JavaScript

Harshal Kahar

Full Stack Web Developer | MERN Stack Web Developer | UI- UX Developer

Ahmedabad, India

å November 2002 ■ harshalskahar389@gmail.com 📞 9537407968

• https://harshalkahar.vercel.app/

⇔ harshal-kahar

narshal255

EDUCATION

L.D. College Of Engineering, Ahmedabad

B.E., Computer Engineering

(October 2020 - Present)

78.1%

Sheth P.H. Vidyalaya, Navsari

Higher secondary, Science Stream (PCM)

(May 2018 - March 2020)

79.85%

PROJECTS

NextSanity Blogfolio (Open Source Plateform)

Developed Nextblog Portfolio plateform, open-source web application aimed at simplifying portfolio creation for aspiring students.

(November 2022 -August 2023)

NextJS empowers Nextblog Portfolio with seamless server-side rendering, ensuring lightning-fast performance and optimized user experiences. Utilizing Sanity CMS with GROQ query language, managing content becomes effortless, allowing users to update their portfolios without delving into complex codebases.

https://github.com/harshal255/NextSanity-Blogfolio

Skills : NextJS \cdot Tailwind CSS \cdot Framer Motion \cdot Sanity Headless CMS \cdot GROQ Query Language \cdot EmailJS \cdot Notion Page

WORK EXPERIENCE

Project Library, @LDCE

Full Stack Developer

(October 2022 - March 2023)

responsible for front-end development of Project Library web application. Develop the web application to provide a platform for students of our computer department to find all, filter as final year projects, and visualize the Dashboard. Skills: ReactJS · Tailwind CSS · ApexchartJS · RechartJS · React Slick · Git · Github

https://harshalkahar.vercel.app/projects/project-library

SKILLS

Core Subjects

DSA,OOP,OS,DBMS,CN

Programming Language

Javascript, C++

Web Development

HTML, CSS, JAVASCRIPT(ES6+), TAILWIND CSS, MATERIAL-TAILWIND CSS, NODEJS REST FULL, EXPRESSJS, REACTJS, NEXTJS, HEADLESS CMS (STRAPI CMS, SANITY.IO)

Database

MongoDB, mySQL

Development Tools

Git, Github, VS code, Replit

Others

Figma, Canva, Notion Page

INTERESTS

Coding, Designing, Chess, Carrom, Exercise